A Guide to the James Hinkle-William Faulkner Research Collection
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
James Hinkle-William Faulkner Research Collection 1835 (1930-1990) and n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11069
Ca. 6,050 items.
This collection of research material compiled by James Hinkle, chiefly concerns William Faulkner and, to a lesser extent, Ernest Hemingway, and consists of ca. 6,050 items, 1835(1930- 1990) and n.d. Included are correspondence, manuscripts, typescripts, student papers, essays and other papers, notes, printed articles, brochures, miscellaneous printed material, and photographs.
James Hinkle-William
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Stored off-site. Users must request boxes 48 hours in advance of desired use. Neither drop-in nor next-day requests can be fulfilled. For additional information, contact Special Collections.
Acquisition Information
This research material was made a gift to the Library by Mrs. Nancy H. Hinkle of Santee, California, on November 10, 1992.
Biographical/Historical Information
James Hinkle conceived the idea of a series--Reading Faulkner--of glossaries of William Faulkner's novels and established its principles, selected the authors, and worked on the various stages of planning and preparation. Hinkle believed that readers must understand each word in Faulkner's novels at its most basic or literal level before beginning to understand the works' larger issues. Hinkle spent much of his scholarly life reading about the South and things Southern, first in printed sources and then in county and city archives. These articles and records are part of this research collection. He was also intrigued by Faulkner's names, and compiled commentaries on their etymologies, their cultural and historical backgrounds, and their pronunciations. He listened to the tapes of Faulkner's readings at the University of Virginia in order to hear how Faulkner himself pronounced the names and words he wrote. The notes concerning Faulkner's names are included among the papers. Following his establishment as a Hemingway scholar, Hinkle began to study Faulkner and his works. He believed that careful reading, exhaustive inquiry, and thoughtful interpretation might allow one to slip inside Faulkner's genius and emerge a better person. He urged his students to study Faulkner with an open and inquisitive mind. Many of his best student essays, questions and answers, and notes are among these papers. [from Reading Faulkner: The Unvanquished PS3511.A86 U537 1995] James Hinkle, professor of English at San Diego State University, taught seminars on Ernest Hemingway and William Faulkner. He delivered several papers at various Hemingway and Faulkner meetings. In Hemingway studies, he was best known for work on The Sun Also Rises, and delivered a speech, "Why the American Family on the Train and the Old Basque on the Bus Are in The Sun Also Rises" at the South Atlantic MLA special SAR session to observe the 60th anniversary of the publication of SAR. He published several articles in the Hemingway Review (1986 Fall, 1982 Fall), and collaborated with other scholars on books on Faulkner, including Reading Faulkner: The Unvanquished and Reading Faulkner: Light in August and contributed an article to William Faulkner -- Materials, Studies, and Criticism (1981 April). OBITUARY. The following was taken from the "Death Notices and Funeral Announcements" of the December 11, 1990 Los Angeles Times: James Currey Hinkle died of massive heart failure on December 5, 1990. Mr. Hinkle was born on December 21, 1923 in Evansville, Indiana and had served in the 3rd Division of the United States Army during World War II as a Technical Writer in North Africa and through the Anzio invasion. He was decorated with the Purple Heart and two Bronze Stars. He married Nancy Hanks Hufstader on August 14, 1948 in Flint, Michigan. He graduated from Denison University in Granville, Ohio, then undertook graduate work at the University of Iowa, the University of Paris, and at Harvard University where he received a Masters degree in American Literature. He then taught at Harvard University, Dickinson College, Denison University, and San Diego State University where he was a faculty member for the last thirty years. His chosen fields of emphasis were the works of William Faulkner and Ernest Heminway. He was active in local youth sports thoughout the '60s and '70s. He is survived by his wife, seven children and six grandchildren. At his request, there will be no funeral service. On February 8, 1991 San Diego State University is having a Memorial service. Memorial contributions may be sent to: American Heart Assoc., San Diego County Chapter, P. O. Box 3625, San Diego, CA 92103.
Contents List
- Research Files on Faulkner's Novels (Othertype 1-3)
  - Absalom, Absalom!:Essays and Questions n.d. (Othertype 1 (A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"The Bear": Essays and Genealogies n.d. (Othertype 1 (A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"The Old People": Typescript with Revisions n.d. (Othertype 1 (A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Article by Hinkle--Comments 1980, 1985 (Othertype 1 (A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Ariticle by Hinkle--First Draft and First Revision 1980 (Othertype 1 (A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Article by Hinkle--Notes 1980 (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Article by Hinkle--Original Version and Revision 1980 (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Article by Hinkle-- Revisions and Notes [1980] (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Article by Hinkle--Worksheets and Notes n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Go Down, Moses--"Was": Typescripts with Revisions n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Intruder in the Dust: Essays by students and Glossary 1965, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Killers: Questions n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Light in August: Essays by Students on Chapter V 1958-1959, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Light in August: Essays by Students on the Promissory Note 1958-1959, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Light in August: Questions and Answers n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Rivers: Questions and Answers n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Sanctuary: Chronology Data n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Sanctuary: Miscellaneous 1988-1990, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Sanctuary:Notes on Chapter I and II n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Sanctuary: Notes on Temple Drake 1985, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Sanctuary: Papers by Noel Polk n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Short Stories: Essays by Students 1971-1976, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Snopes Trilogy-- The Hamlet: Breakdwon and Notes 1987, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Snopes Trilogy-- The Hamlet: Louis Daneil Brodsky 1985 (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - Snopes Trilogy-- The Hamlet: Chronology 1964-1970, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Hamlet Essays and Ideas 1980-1987 (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Hamlet Essays on the "Missing Dash" 1983 (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Hamlet Essays on "Poor Labove" 1986, n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15))
  - The Hamlet Glossary--First Revision n.d. (Othertype 2 folders)
  - The Hamlet Glossary Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Hamlet Glossary 32-189 n.d., 4 folders (Othertype 1(A25-15A))
  - The Hamlet Glossary 190-372 n.d., 4 folders (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Manuscript (from the University of Virginia) n.d., 2 folders (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Noel Polk 1986-1987 (Othertype 2A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--with Answers n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Question -- Barbara's Answers and Notes n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions -- Hubert Campbell's Notes n.d., 2 folders (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions -- Draft with Answers n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Future n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15A))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Original n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Original with Answers n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Revised A-L21 n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Second Revision n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Seond Revision A1-M7 n.d., 2 folders (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Questions--Recond Revision A1-M7, Answers n.d., 2 folders (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Text--with Noel Polk's Revisions n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Typescript first pages and Notes 1981, n.d. (Othertype 2(A25-15B))
  - The Hamlet Typescript Setting Copy (from the University of Virginia) n.d., 4 folders (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Hamlet Worksheets n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Hamlet Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Town Chronology and Genealogy n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Town: Questions--with Answers n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Town: Questions--Original n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Sound and the Fury: Glossary and Notes n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Sound and the Fury: Text n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Essays by Students 1975, 1977, n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary--"Ambuscade" 1986 (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary--Buff Cover n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary--Cartoons and Pictures n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary--Green Cover 1986 (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary--Originals n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary--Purple Cover n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Glossary-- Reprints 1986 (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Ideas for Papers 1977-1985 (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Miscellaneous 1980-1981, n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Quizzes n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Quizzes 11-266 n.d. (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
  - The Unvanquished: Text--with Noel Polk's Revisions n.d., 3 folders (Othertype 3(A25-15C))
- Research Files on Faulkner Miscellaneous (Othertype 4-6)
  - Annotation Series n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Bibliographies n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Bibliography: by Thomas L. McHaney [1989] (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Chronology n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Civil War n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Collections and Exhibits n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Commenmorative Stamp 1987 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Conferences: Colloquium, Paris, France and Salamanca, Spain 1980, 1984 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Conferences: Faulkner and Yoknapatawpha Conference, University of Mississippi 1974-1983 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Conferences: Faulkner and Yoknapatawpha conference, University of Mississippi--Notes 1979-1984 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Conferences: Faulkner Conference, San Diego State University 1985-1987 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Conferences: Miscellaneous 1986-1988 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertations: Abstracts 1972-1980, n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertations: Abstracts--Have or Read 1951-1968, 3 folders (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertations: Abstracts--Heminway--Have or Read 1948-1977 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertations: Faulkner--Miscellaneous 1984-1987, n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertation: Hemingway--Miscellaneous 1983, n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertation: Lists n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertations: Orders 1972-1980, n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Dissertations: Women 1970, n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Glossary: Letters to Explicators 1986-1989 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Handwriting 1987 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Hymns n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Idealism: Paper, "the Limits of Faulkner's Idealism" by James Hinkle 1980 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Ideas for Papers 1980-1986 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Literature: William Blake 1970 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Literature: Contemporary Poets/Poets n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Literature: E. E. Cummings 1934-1971 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Literature: Emily Dickinson 1958, 1974 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature: Norman Douglas 1939 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature:Nathaniel Hawthorne 1953-1959, n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature:Gerard Manley Hopkins n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature: Johnson/Jonson 1957, 1964 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature: John Keats n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature: Walt Kelly n.d. (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature: Knowledge and Use--Paper by Calvin S. Brown 1982 (Othertype 4(A25-15D))
  - Lietrature: Ross Lockridge 1962-1972 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Herman Melville 1953 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Edgar Allan Poe 1954-1976 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Laurence Sterne 1957-1970 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Theory--A-WWW n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theory--A- WWW, yellow sheets n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theory--XXX-JJJ n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theory--10W-35WY2 n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theroy-- 14Y1-25Y2 n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theory--Articles 1985-1988 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theory--Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Lietrature: Theory--Paper, "About Literature and What to do With It," n.d., Orginal, copy 2 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Literature: Theory--Paper, "About Literature and What to do With It," n.d., Original, yellow sheets (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Literature: Theory--Paper, "About Literature and What to do With It," Second Version, yellow sheets n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Theory--Paper, "About Literature and What to do With It," Second Version n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Literature: Dylan Thomas 1958-1969 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Literature: Thomas Wolfe n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Brochures 1967-1981, n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Brochures--Holly Springs 1950, 1973 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Brochures--Oxford 1966-1979, n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Geography and Topography 1941, 1962 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Geography and Topography-- Of Men and Rivers by Gary B. Mills 1978 (Othertype 5(A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Geology and Geomorphology 1981 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Maps 1963-1976, n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Maps--Oxford [1970s] (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Maps--Oxford--Notes and Worksheets 1973, n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Maps--Oxford--Notes and Worksheets for 1920 Map 1979, n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Maps--Oxford--Utilities and Courthouse--Oxford n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Telephone Directories 1959, 1972 (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Mississippi: Treaties n.d. (Othertype 5 (A25-15E))
  - Names: Articles, "What to Call Faulkner's Characters" by James Hinkle 1981 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Book # 1 and #2 n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Characters n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Miscellaneous 1985-1986 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Original List n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Pronunciation 1981, n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Yoknapatawpha: Notes--Preliminary n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Yoknapatawpha: Paper, "Some Yoknapatawpha Names" by James Hinkle--Condensed and Final versions n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Yoknapatawpha: Paper, "Some Yoknapatawpha Names" by James Hinkle--Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Names: Yoknapatawpha: Paper, "Some Yoknapatawpha Names" by James Hinkle--Mississippi version n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15))
  - Names: Yoknapatawpha: Paper, "Some Yoknapatawpha Names" by James Hinkle--Oxford version n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15))
  - Names: Yoknapatawpha: Paper, "Some Yoknapatawpha Names" by James Hinkle--Printed n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Newsletters 1932, 1981, 1989 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Newsletters: Sonopes Pay 1972-1977, 3 folders (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Notes: Universities Collections 1981-1983 (Othertype 6 A26-15F))
  - Notes: University of Virginia Collection 1976-1981 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Textual Editing n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner-- Absalom, Absalom!n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Characters in Yoknapatawpha County 1955 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Choctaw Indians 1949 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Civil War 1968 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Dialect 1966 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Dialect--Peculiarities of Mississippi Speech 1893 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Difficult Short Stories 1954 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Duelling 1924 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Col. W. C. Falkner 1969 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner-- Go Down, Moses1963 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Lafayette County 1935 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner-- Lafayette County 1939 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--"Lucas Beauchamp" 1962 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Snopes Trilogy 1965 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Structure of Short Stories 1957 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Yoknapatawpha and Lafayette Counties 1949,1958 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Thesis: Faulkner--Yoknapatawpha County Statistics 1963 (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Topics: Lists for Filecards and Folders n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Words and Pharases--use: Answers to Questions made by Calvin S. Brown n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Writings--Novels and Short Stories: Lists 1965, n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
  - Yoknapatawpha: Miscellaneous n.d. (Othertype 6 (A25-15F))
- Articles re Faulkner's Novels and Short Stories (Othertype 4)
  - Articles: Absalom, Absalom! 1945-1986, 14 folders (Othertype 7 (A25-15G))
  - Articles: As I Lay Dying 1943-1984, 8 folders (Othertype 7 (A25-15G))
  - Articles: Characters--Gavin Stevens 1953-1969 (Othertype 7 (A25-15G))
  - Articles: A Fable 1954-1955 (Othertype 7 (A25-15G))
  - Articles: Genealogies 1966, n.d. (Othertype 7 (A25-15G))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses 1952-1984, 4 folders (Othertype 7 (A25-15G))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses--"The Bear" and Text 1942-1985, 7 folders (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses--"Delta Autumn" 1963-1984 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses--"The Fire and the Hearth," and Text 1940, 1963-1985 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses--"The Old People," and Text 1940, 1950-1982 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses--"Pantaloon in Black," and Text 1940, 1962-1983 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Go Down, Moses--"Was" 1949-1985 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Intruder in the Dust 1948-1979, 2 folders (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Knight's Gambit 1954-1978 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Light in August 1935-1986, 7 folders (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Notes for a Horsethief Text 1950 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Ariticles: Old Man 1952-1969 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Pylon 1957-1979 (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: The Reivers 1962-1977, 2 folders (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Requiem for a Nun 1952-1975, 2 folders (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: 1933-1974, 3 folders (Othertype 8 (A25-15H))
  - Articles: Sanctury 1975-1986, 2 folders (Othertype 9 (A25- 16 A))
  - Articles: Sartoris 1952-1984, 3 folders (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Ambuscade, " Text 1934 (Othertype 9(A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"And Now What's to Do" 1973 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Barn Burning," and Text 1934, 1959-1983 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"A Bear Hunt," and Text 1934, 163-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Big Woods" 1980 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"By the People," Text 1955 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Carcassone" 1925 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories-- "Centaur in Brass," Text 1932 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"A Courtship," and Text 1948, 1963-1981 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Death Drag," and Text 1932, 1964-1971 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Dry September" 1931, 1952-1984 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Elly," and Text 1934, 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Fool About a Horse," Text 1936 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Fox Hunt," Text 1931 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"God Down, Moses," and Text 1941, 1985 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Gold is Not Always," Text 1940 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Hair," and Text 1931, 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Hand Upon the Waters," Text 1939 (Othertype 9 ( A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"The Hound," and Text 1931, 1957 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--Indian Stories 1967-1978 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"A Justice" 1954-1974 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Lion," Text 1935 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Lizards in Jamshyd's Courtyard," Text 1932 (Othertype ( (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Lo!" 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Mississippi," Text 1954 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Monk," Text 1937 (Othertype ( (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Mountain Victory," and Text 1932, 1964-1979 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Mule in the Yard," Text 1934 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"My Grandmother Millard...," and Text 1943,1963-1970 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"A Name for the City," Text 1950 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Once Aboard the Lugger" 1978 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"A Point of Law," Text 1940 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Race at Morning," and Text 1955, 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Raid," Text 1934 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Red Leaves," and Text 1930, 1954-1979 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Retreat," Text 1934 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Riposte in Tertio," Text 1936 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"A Rose for Emily," and Text 1930, 1943-1984, 4 folders (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Sepulture South," and Text 1955, [1970] (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Shall Not Perish," and Text 1943, 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Shingles For the Lord, " and Text 1943, 1959-1975 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Skirmish at Sartoris," Text 1935 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Smoke," Text 1932 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"Sotted Horses," and Text 1931, 1962-1979 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"The Tall Men'" and Text 1941, 1962-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"That Evening Sun" 1931, 1935-1983, 2 folders (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"That Will Be Find," and Text 1935, 1964-1969 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))
  - Articles: Short Stories--"There Was a Queen," and Text 1933, 1964-1975 (Othertype 9 (A25-16A))